Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 91st Congress, 1963-1970; Undated; 7; 11.2 cubic ft.
  - H. R. 17698: A Bill for Amendment of Title 32 of the United States Code, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 17725: A Bill to Provide that All Federally Assisted Child Day-Care Programs Shall Provide, as a Part of Such Program, Nutritional Meals and Preventative, Diagnostic, and Emergency Medical Care, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 17763: A Bill for Amendment of the Older Americans Act of 1965, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 17828: A Bill for Amendment of the Higher Education Facilities Act of 1963, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - H. R> 17835: A Bill for Amendment of Section 401 of the Federal Aviation Act of 1958, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 17840: A Bill for Amendment of Title 6 of the Civil Rights Act of 1964, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 17857: A Bill to Abolish the Death Penalty Under All Laws of the United States, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - H. R. 17858: A Bill to Provide a Program of National Health Insurance (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - H. R. 17858: A Bill to Provide a Program of National Health Insurance (2of 2), 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - H. R. 18398: A Bill for Amendment of Section 620 of the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - H. R. 18429: A Bill to Promote and Protect the Free Flow of Interstate Commerce Without Unreasonable Damage to the Environment, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - H. R. 18451: A Bill to Amend the Truth in Lending Act to Require that Statements Under Open End Credit Plans be Mailed in Time to Permit Payment Prior to the Imposition of Finance Charges, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 18593: A Bill for Amendment of Fish and Wildlife Coordination Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 18614: A Bill for Voluntary Military Manpower Procurement Act of 1970 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 18893: A Bill to Permit Any of Certain Municipalities to be Considered as a "State" for the Purpose of Applying for Benefits Under Certain Federal Grant-in-Aid Programs, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 18926: A Bill for Amendment of Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 18927: A Bill to Require Certain Newspapers to Provide a Balanced and Substantially Complete Presentation of Issues of Public Importance (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 18927: A Bill to Require Certain Newspapers to Provide a Balanced and Substantially Complete Presentation of Issues of Public Importance (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 18928: A Bill for Amendment of Section 4 of the Newspaper Preservation Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 18929: A Bill for Amendment of Title 10 of the United States Code to Require that Enlisted Members of the Armed Forces be Given Upon Request, Certain Examinations in Spanish, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 18980: A Bill for the Abatement of Air Pollution by the Control of Emissions from Motor Vehicles, Motor Vehicle Engines, Stationary Sources, and Fuel and Fuel Additives in Order to Protect the Health and Welfare of the People of the United States, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 18986: A Bill for Amendment of the Truth in Lending Act, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 18988: A Bill to Reduce Pollution Which is Caused by Litter Composed of Soft Drink and Beer Containers, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 19034: A Bill for Amendment of Title 2 of the Federal Aviation Act of 1958, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 19035: A Bill for Amendment of Title 10 of the United States Code to Require that Enlisted Members of the Armed Forces be Given Upon Request, Certain Examinations in Spanish, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 19334: A Bill to Promote Public Health and Welfare by Expanding, Improving, and Better Coordinating the Family Planning Services and Population Research Activities of the Federal Government, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 19368: A Bill to Establish a Juvenile Research Institute and Training Center, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 19417: A Bill to Establish a Transportation Trust Fund to Encourage Mass Transportation, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 19453: A Bill for Amendment of the Clean Air Act, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 19745: A Bill to Facilitate and Encourage Cooperation Between the United States and Certain Defense Contractors Engaged in the Furnishing of Defense Material in the United States, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - H. Res. 67: A Resolution for Amendment of the R ules of the House of Representatives to Abolish the Committee on Un-American Activities and to Enlarge the Jurisdiction of the Committee on the Judiciary, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - H. Res. 226: A Resolution for Expressing the Sense of the House of Representatives with Respect to the Restoration of Human Rights in Iraq (Also Contains Related Bills), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - H. Res. 241: A Resolution for United States Aid for Iraqi Jews, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - H. Res. 307: A Resolution for Abolishment of the Committee on Internal Security and Enlarge the Jurisdiction of the Committee on the Judiciary, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - H. Res. 390: A Resolution to Express the Sense of the House Regarding the Shutdown of Job Corps Installations Before Congressional Authorization and Appropriation Actions, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - H. Res. 421: A Resolution to Provide for the Emigration of Iraqi Jews, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - H. Res. 457: A Resolution Urging the President to Resubmit for Ratification that Geneva Protocol of 1925 Banning the First-Use of Gas and Bacteriological Warfare, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - H. Res. 465: A Resolution Seeking Agreement with the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics on Limiting Offensive and Defensive Strategic Weapons and the Suspension of Test Flights of Reentry Vehicles, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - H. Res. 529: A Resolution Urging the President of the United States to Take Whatever Action May be Necessary to Stop Air Piracy (Also Contains H. Con. Res. 461), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - H. Res. 542: A Resolution to Establish a Select Committee of the House of Representatives to Investigate the Relocation of the Naval Applied Science Laboratory in Brooklyn, New York, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - H. Res. 607: A Resolution in Support of a Cease-Fire and Accelerated United States Troop Withdrawal from Vietnam, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - H. Res. 699: A Resolution for Withdrawal of United States Forces in South Vietnam on an Orderly and Fixed Schedule, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - H. Res. 906: A Resolution Calling for a National Commitment to Cure and Control Cancer Within This Decade, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - H. Res. 933: A Resolution Expressing the Sense of the House that the President Implement the Majority Report of the Cabinet Task Force on Oil Import Control, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - H. Res. 935: A Resolution Expressing the Support of the House of Representatives with Respect to the Strategic Arms Limitation Talks, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - H. Res. 962: A Resolution Expressing the Sense of the House of Representatives with Respect to Any Military Action Involving the United States in Cambodia, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - H. Res. 974: A Resolution to Designate May 8, 1970 as a National Day of Mourning for the Kent State University Students (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - H. Res. 1003: A Resolution to Set an Expenditure Limitation on the American Military Effort in Southeast Asia (Also Contains H. Con. Res. 616), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - H. Res. 1087: A Resolution Calling for a National Commitment to Cure and Control Cancer Within This Decade, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - H. Res. 1173: A Resolution Expressing the Sense of the House of Representatives with Respect to Balance of Power in the Middle East, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - H. Res. 1202: A Resolution Urging the President to Take Unilateral Action, As Well As Collective Action Through the United Nations, To Stop Air Piracy, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - H. Res. 1208: A Resolution for Amendment of the Rules of the House of Representatives to Create a Standing Committee to be Known as the Committee on the Environment, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Health, Education and Welfare Department, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Highway Amendment for Replacement of Low Income Housing Stock Destroyed as Result of Highway Construction, 1969-11-25 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hudson Guild: Conference on Consumer Problems of Older People, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Housing and Urban Development Department, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Housing and Urban Development Food Trades High School, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Hunger Information, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Justification of Appropriation Estimates for Fiscal Year 1970 (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Justification of Appropriation Estimates for Fiscal Year 1970 (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Lower Eastside Neighborhoods Association Proposal for Tenement Improvement and Landlord Tenant Cooperation, 1967; 1969 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Maritime Administration, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Merchant Marines, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Neighborhood Medical Centers, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - North East Neighborhood Association, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Chinese Youth Council, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: East Village Girls Club, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Health Clinics, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Neighborhood Health Council Regarding Gouverneur Hospital (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Lower East Side Neighborhood Health Council Regarding Gouverneur Hospital (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Mobilization for Youth, Inc. Adult Basic Education, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Operation Outreach, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: The Real Great Society, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Women's Talent Corps, Inc., 1967; 1969 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: Women's Talent Corps College for Human Services, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Annual Reports, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Foreign Aid Investment Reports (1 of 2), 1966; 1969 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Foreign Aid Investment Reports (2 of 2), 1961; 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Javits' Bill in Senate, 90th Congress on Quasi-Public Corporation, 1965; 1968 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Legislative Papers, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Office of Economic Opportunity Reports, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Press Releases and Statements on Quasi-Public Corporation Bill H. R. 11244, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Proposals, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Quasi-Government Corporation Reports, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Quasi-Government Corporation Report and Legislation, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Reports (1 of 3), 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Reports (2 of 3), 1965-1967; 1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Reports (3 of 3), 1957; 1962-1963; 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Overseas Private Investment Corporation: Working Drafts on Quasi-Public Corporation Bill, H. R. 11244, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pan Am Heliport, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Peace Corps, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Post Office Department, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Post Office Department, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Post Office Department: Morgan Station Post Office and Housing (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Post Office Department: Morgan Station Post Office and Housing (2 of 2), 1962; 1965-1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Public Works Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Public Works S. 1648: Public Works and Economic Development Act, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Service Academies, 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Subcommittee on Europe, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Subcommittee on Europe, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Subcommittee on Europe: Hearings on Spanish Bases, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Subcommittee on Europe: Soviet Jewry, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - West Point -[RESTRICTED], 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Congressional Record Inserts, 1957-1970; 8; 4 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically
  The papers found in this series consist of only congressional record inserts during Farbstein's time in office.
  - Assorted Topics, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Topics, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Topics, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Topics, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 3), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 3), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 3), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 3), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 3), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 3), 1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 4), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 4), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 4), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 4), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 4), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 4), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 4), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 4), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 5), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 5), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 5), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 5), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Topics (5 of 5), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 4), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 4), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 4), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 4), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 8), 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Topics (5 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Assorted Topics (6 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Assorted Topics (7 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Assorted Topics (8 of 8), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Assorted Topics (1 of 4), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Assorted Topics (2 of 4), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Assorted Topics (3 of 4), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Assorted Topics (4 of 4), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 11)